KhurramSultan Pakistan Subtitles
John Wick: Chapter 3 (2019)
subscene.com
"AbRam to"
Do you have been moved at all?
.Almost
Sir, With all due respect, are you sure that this is the best option for us?
...Why can't we just take
Because my nephew fucking
.Killed the dog
.Steal a car
...Steal a car
.Is currently in our possession.
So, are we having everything for the car?
.It's not just a car
.(It's a car (John Wick
If you don't live by it?
.He killed my nephew.
.And my brother also
.Dozens of my men.
.Compared to his car.
.And dragged him
Do you think he will stop now?
Sir, he's one man
Why don't we spend it?
...(John Wick)
A man with a high concentration
Committed to
Will come back here inevitably
I once killed three guys in a bar.
.With a pen, I know I heard the story...
.By a fucking pen
Who can do that?
...I can assure you
...The stories I've heard about this guy.
If it wasn't .It has been distorted
.I took my car.
"The boogeyman=a scary guy."
Peace
Can a man like me that knows peace?
.Why don't
Peace
.Enjoy a period of retirement.
(Mr. (Wick
"John Wick, Part II"
Hi, buddy.
Naughty Dog
What are you doing, (John)?
I look at you
What then are you? - I'm waiting for you.
Come here
Hey, kid.
You have somewhere safe and nice here.
(Hello (free - hi -
John), what the hell is this?) .I thought you loved this car
What do you think?
Well, the engine is about to fall
Structure, arched full
The steering axis has been completely destroyed.
I don't know if you noticed or not .But you broke the windshield
I mean...what can I do?
I can fix it
Thank you for the find.
No problem dude, I've .I made some of the calls
.Not a big deal.
Let me know when you fix it.
Well
Will be ready by Christmas
The year 2030
(Hi (John
(Santino)
Can I come in?
Of course
Do you want coffee?
Thanks
Nice to see you.
Nice to see you also
I'm sorry to hear what happened on (wife, you, (John
Thank you
...What about the dog does he have a name?
All
(Listen, (John
Sincerely
I don't want to be here.
Please, don't do
I'm asking you not to do this.
I'm sorry
No one
...Went out again returned
Without side effects
(I did this with a heavy heart, my (John
But remember this ...
If you don't perform the purpose for which it was made for?
By the night of your task impossible
.You shouldn't be here, in case this simple.
What you are now is thanks to my
It's mine in particular
Start
Relive it in? - Yeah, get it back. -
(The brand is not something easy hey (John
For a man who hates another man by the
It represents the Association of the spirit and the blood.
Find someone else to take it
Listen to me
What is this?
Do you remember?
.This is your blood.
You came to me.
I helped you
If you don't accept to do this.
.You know what the consequences...
.I'm not that person anymore.
.I've always been that person, John.
.I can't help you.
.I'm sorry
.Yeah, you're right.
.You can't
.But "is" can
(See you soon, (John
(You have the House Beautiful, (John
Bye
What is the cause of the fire according to you, (John)?
The gas leak?
Yeah, gas leak
Are you back again?
(Nice to see you, (c
!Come on, Boy.
Good night, (John)
!Fuck
I want to see the director
.(I am happy to see you again so soon, Mr. (Wick
Do you want to tell him that?
.Yes, please.
.Stay here
.Mr. (Wick) on his way to see you, sir.
.It's flawless
.Put her in the field of trading
Where is it?
.Thank you, my friend.
.Nice work
What are you doing, (Jonathan) is?
.I burned down my house
.He refused the brand that gave .You're lucky he did it only
What were you thinking what the hell
(Set to "mark" a guy like (Santino D'antonio.
It was the only way .Stay out of work
You call this a departure from the work?
What do you think will happen?
What do you expect?
You really thought that this day couldn't have come at all?
What he wants you to do?
.I didn't ask him
.She only refused
There are two rules you can't get them out (Oh (Jonathan
No bloodshed in the territory of the European
.And the relationship must withstand the condition
My judgment comes in the case of cancellation of the decision of the final isolation come
Table "a responsible adult"
Have their methods special in the contract in case you refuse them any request
.I have no choice
If you betray the "brand" will be the
If you kill the carrier "brand" will be the
.If I run away, you die
(This is what did you part with them, (Jonathan
.Do what they want from you
.When they are free
(Then, if you want to go behind (Santino
If I wanted to burn his house to the ground.
.When will be my guest ...but until then ...
Abide by the rules
.Exactly, abide by the rules
.Without them, we will work with animals
Can you take animals?
I'm sorry to say that.
.But this hotel does not accept animals...
I'm any case it would be my pleasure to take that responsibility.
It also want to.
.I appreciate it.
Does he have a name, Sir?
All
.Naughty Dog
.Stay here
.This was my father's collection
I can see a lot, not just draw .On the canvas of course
.But I found myself here.
.Prefer
(I didn't want to do it, (John
If you came to retire
.When will honor it.
.Look for yourself
You think about it, isn't it?
.You're no longer exits.
.The guards
.When assaulted me in time
I wonder what way would you do it?
.With a pen, that woman
.Or by a crutch that man
.Maybe by his glasses.
.By hands
.How exciting
With it, you know that you can't do that right?
.I told you, I want that man that I was.
The way you look at me right now.
I want the "bogeyman" creepy guy
(I want (John Wick
Just tell me what do you want exactly?
.I want you to kill my sister.
Why?
There are 12 seats at the table responsible adult
(Camorra), (mafia), (Andrea)
(Chinese), (Russian)
...When my father died.
.Lost gave it his special seat.
They represent the (Camorra) now
I can't say, but I wonder
What I would like to achieve instead?
...You want me to kill
(Gianni De Antonio)
.I wouldn't do that at all.
.She's my flesh and blood
I still love her
Can't do that. (it's in the (Rome -
.To expect
...You have to climb through the tunnels - no matter where she is.
...This
.(I need the ghost (John Wick
.That's why I need you.
.Do this for me.
.And your will be gracing its
What would you say?
"I don't want to waste the dog"
5903.5.
(Happy hunting, Mr. (Wick
"Welcome to the land of Europe in Rome"
"How am I supposed to help you?"
"I'll take the room"
(Jonathan)
(Julius)
Hi - nice to see you.
I failed to call you back. when I was in Rome another time
...And I've heard
.You have retired
Right
...If you have to answer
One question
Are you here for the (pope) is?
All
.Well then
.One of the best rooms we have
.Thank you
.Enjoy your stay
(Mr. (Wick
Are "bartender" here?
.I've never known him does not exist "do you mean, he's always there"
(Good evening, Mr. (Wick
.It's been a long time
I would like to drink a little
.I'm very excited to show you something.
.First
(Good morning, Mr. (Wick
(Hi (Angela
Welcome back to Rome.
Do you want to get you a new suit?
For
(I know you're in the past like the (parents German
But let me introduce you to a new class (of (Austria
Gun (O'clock) at a rate of 34 mm and 26 mm
This is the original map for the (de Antonio)
.You have here all the ancient monuments
Tell me, Mr. (Wick), is it a formal event or issue social?
.Social cause - is it in the morning or in the evening? -
I want one for the morning .And for the evening
.With handle for precise control
.Flats Mako file), in order to re-filling easier)
.I know you will pay for the design of the openings
What's next?
.I want one strong and delicate at the same time
.Strong and delicate
This is a map of the complex and tunnels under the .The surface of the Earth
What is the style that you want? - Italian -
How many buttons do you want? - Two -
Pants? - ."Spindle-shaped "tapered -
What about the card suits?
.Tactical
"Integrity "no R-15
11.5 inch
.With bolt carrier offers the characteristics of the novel in "the Bolt is part of the chain have the form of a stick thin long"
(As well as with speakers standard (1-6
.This is a planned modern with color blue
.There are from one to two to three gates
"Tablets "carbide Silicon
.Footnote composed of ceramic
.A protective shield for the hull accompanied by the cans
I sewed between the fabric of the cloth .Lining
.Rate hack = zero
Anyway
.I'm afraid to be very painful
Do you recommend anything useful for the end of the night?
.Something large and powerful
...Can I suggest you
"Benelli M4"
,Designed on the basis of the Zapper easy to control .As well as easy in re-feed
Knob scheme
.In case your hands have become wet, the two
.Italian classic
.Talk time "means the last weapon"
Dessert?
.Knives the best ever.
.The industry has been newly
!Well done
Can you send an immediate request to? - Certainly I can.
Where do you want to send it to you? - .To the hotel.
Do you want to send everything to your own room?
.For
.Thanks. -Excellent.
.(Mr. (Wick
.Enjoy at your own
.Good evening
Are you enjoying the party?
.Excuse me, ma'am.
.Mr. (waking up) waiting for you.
.I'll be there in one moment
(Mr. (Akoni
Do you enjoy the festival?
.Thank you for seeing me
.Sit down, please.
(Mrs. (D'antonio
You can't take what is rightfully his - not taken anything.
Those who are among your followers has encroached our property
.I've been cutting their throats with a knife.
What is the evidence?
Besides ...
That knife that I talked about .Was meant for the children of your followers is not
.The Follow had to watch it only
.What you have become to us now.
(Mr. (Akoni
And now I leave.
.Enjoy the party
.Get yourself some fun.
Why don't you go and do the hospitality arrangements, etc. for our guests
While I renew your make-up to me?...
.Well, ma'am.
What can I do without you, (Cassian) is?
(John)
(Jian)
It's been a long time we think of ourselves ...do like
.Chosen
.Still further
.And now here you are.
.Envoy to important to kill
What brings you back again, (John)?
"Mark"
How so?
.By your brother.
(Tell me (John
"This "tag
Security during her leave work?
...And what is her name
The woman whose life ended my life?...
(Helen)
Helen) this)
Is worth the price you pay now?
And now ...
Let me tell you what will happen when I die.
Santino) will demand the My Own in) Table officials large
Will take on the New York
.We also
By the assistance .Are you gonna get her Don't
What was she (Helen) will be based about the (John) it?
What was she (Helen) will you?
Why?
.Because I lived my life the way I want
.And I will die the way I want
Are you afraid of the car, (John)?
.For
...You know
.I always thought I could run away through it.
.What I see now coming
.What I see is you
(John)
(Cassian)
Do you work here?
.For
What about you? - Me too.
.Good night
.I'm afraid it is.
.I'm sorry to hear that.
.Seize him!
.He (John Wick) Force arrested
A dead end?
Only one
For
I've had a good night, don't you, (John)?
Gentlemen
Do I have to remind you of leadership
There should be no work .Connected to the land and European
.No, sir.
No, sir.
Now may I suggest you do .To pay a visit to the bar.
.In order to relieve yourselves.
Jane), isn't it?)
.For
(Bourbon)
Right?
For
Thanks
.Thank you
"I have a "relationship
To whom?
.Her brother
...I see you
.Didn't have a choice
He wanted the special rapporteur in the officials ' table .Large
.Gonna get it now.
For
.If you're free now.
Am I free?
All
.At all.
"I have killed "my word=ma'am
.Someone close to me.
(An eye for an eye Hey (John
You know how it goes.
For
.I'll make it quick.
.I promise
.I appreciate it
.I'll try to do the same.
.This time on my account
.Consider it a professional courtesy.
You had a busy night huh?
Can I buy you a drink?
.All
.Thanks
,Is not .But I
(See you later, (John Wick
.Not if I see you first.
(Hi (John
.I'm superior to you, if you're upset now
.I know they may be personally.
...But what kind of man would I be
.If I didn't get revenge for my sister...
(John)
Can you inform the board that I will .Pay the bill in the morning.
.With you working the booth
How do you want to draw the call?
(Accounts (Pepi - one moment, please.
(With unit of account of the (Baby How can I help you?
I'd like to open an account - what is the name of the account? -
(John Wick)
Verification code
930-05.
The case of the contract? - Open -
Category?
.Seven million
.Processing, please wait
I appreciate your service. my pleasure.
.You will find a safe passage down.
.The means of transport waiting for you.
.(I wish you a safe journey, Mr. (Wick
.I'm sorry, I'm totally confused
.Order has been confirmed
What is this?
.I get it done.
Brand" over a"
."Put "tag
If not Mr. (Wick) is already dead.
.Will die soon
.Put the "tag" you, sir.
...You have no idea
.What is coming to you...
All the men in the (New York) looking for him.
...I doubt
.We'll see it again.
Did you know ...
.You have stabbed the devil in the back...
Has been forced back to life .Leave it just
.I burned the temple Prince
.I burned back to the boat
."Now he's free of "his relationship
What do you think he will?
Have a glimpse of the other side .And he may embrace it! strongly
(But you, Mr. (D'antonio
.Have taken this aspect away from him.
.He was coming in advance
.It's back for love and not for you.
.He owes me
.I have a right to it.
...But for now
.Has returned again...
.I told you not to do it
.I warned you in advance
.(Goodbye, (Antonio
The knife had entered your artery aortic "aortic artery is the longest artery in the body"
If you pull the knife you'll bleed even .The
.Consider it a professional courtesy.
"If you see anything suspicious."
"What you see is a nightmare, mate."
.Take me to him.
.(Tell him I (John Wick
"You know, buddy, they put it in everything."
"Hey, buddy, I got your phone call."
!As I live and breathe
(John Wick)
"The man"
"Myth, The Legend."
.It seems that you are not good in matters of retirement
.I'm working on it.
Mr. (Wick) don't remember, but we met .Many years ago
.Such as the period of the rise of power
.When I was just a pawn in the game
.When we met he gave me a gift
.The gift that made me a king
You don't remember, but when I was .Standing there in the alley.
.I didn't even hear you when you came
.You gave me this
"The gift of the "bogeyman
.Gift integrated for every occasion
.But you also gave me an option
To pull my gun, and fired it from behind you .And then you die.
...Or continue to "pressure" on my neck.
.When its live
.As you can see now, has survived
.No one can betray me anymore.
.Thanks to you
.Because I always see
.Always know
.If you know why I'm here.
.For (Santino de Antonio), yes.
(Hold your own is over, (John
.This is not good for your health
What is the figure now, (Earl) is?
!Seven million
.Fuck
.It's Christmas Eve
.We're going to the (bar) after this
.I need your help.
You have the eyes through the shoppers for everything .Happens in every corner of the city
.(I think you can find (Santino
.I want you to guide me
.Underground
.Point me to him.
.How cool is that
.The boogeyman" is available to me to help him."
.(Well, of course, (John
.(Yes, (John), whatever you want to him, (John
Do you want me to massage your back, too, (John)?
.You will help me.
.Why hell would I do that
.I am the only person who can help you
!Help me
All of the leaders are the highest ranking of you (Mr (Wick
.Looks very optimistic
But look around you.
What is the amount of plugin which I have do I need?
It seems to me that the real question ...(, Mr. (Wick
Is, of in our world is cruel, this may accept to help you?
.There's a storm coming
...Not just me
.But for everyone
Both are less than .Table officials large
Yeah, killing someone who has a seat at the table ...big
.May creates a problem...
.But it's your problem, buddy.
After all, no one of my men has sent
Gianni De Antonio) to die)...
.I've ever had it now.
.Santino) has her seat now)
.Now he wants the entire city
When going to take over the city, do you think he will stop at 14th Street is?
.We just have to believe ourselves.
Yeah?
For how long?
As the blood that will fall out?
...(You're killing (Santino
The the(Camorra) and the big table... it will be yours
...(I kill (Santino
.They would be mine...
.He offered 7 million dollars for your death.
Seven million dollars, it's a lot of money (sir (Wick
.So, I think if you have a choice
...Do you want war
.Or you can give me a weapon. just...
.To one what this guy weapon please
"Kimber 1911" "a-C-P 45"
.With a capacity of 7 bullets
Seven bullets?
.Seven million dollars will give you seven bullets.
.This means for every bullet a million, buddy.
.Come on.
.(Your way to hell starts from here, Mr. (Wick
.It's in the museum
.Earl) will help you, be careful on your way)
.Remember
.You owe me
.You don't want me to be indebted to you
.Welcome to all
Let's have a toast for the future of the large table .And certainly for the memory of my dear sister
Mr. (Akoni), how are you?
Wick) here.)
.For
.You and you, come with me .You go
Welcome to the reflection of the Spiritual" "the modern in New York
In this second section, the method of interaction ...the lights and the nature of the personal image
List of colors offering you a beautiful experience in ,the display lights
We hope that this presentation has provided you new insights
...In order to understand the world, it is likely just
That leads you to a reflection of deeper into the nature of sound
(God, (John
.God
Don't you get it?
(Mark" are over, (John"
.You should run away.
.You know what you're gonna do the(Camorra) your
Do you think you're as you are in the Old Testament?
(Not (John
.All
.Killing me will end the contract
.Killing me will make it worse.
(John)
You know what I think?
I think you're addicted to it
.Addicted to revenge...
Welcome to the reflection of the Spiritual" "the modern in New York
.Without a wife
.Without life
.Without a home
...Revenge.
.Is all you have
.You wanted me to come back
.And here I am back
.Go, I'll finish it
.See you later
.Definitely
.Good evening
Is the director available?
...Director
.Always present...
(Winston)
(Mr. (de Antonio
.Your night was good as I see
.The search for a safe haven, I guess.
.I want to cancel the membership immediately.
In the eyes of this institution Mr. (Wick) didn't .Out any legitimate law
If you know if I have the right ...to demand B
(Nothing, you're not asking me something, Mr. (de Antonio
.This kingdom is mine, mine alone.
.Right
If you enjoy Kingdom of you, (Winston) as long as .You can do it.
.And you, you honor us, sir.
(I'm here to see (Santino de Antonio
.He's waiting in the hallway, Sir.
"Card greasy"
Makes everything different.
(Jonathan) - have you seen the list of food here? -
Or options request?
.Jonathan), listen to me.)
I can Guest That stays here .For a long time
.And don't eat the same thing twice
.Jonathan), just back off)
.Yes, (Jonathan), stay away
!What did you do?
.I finished it
How was it?
.He was a good dog .I enjoyed his company.
.Let's go home
(Mr. (Wick
.If you have a desire about it.
.Come on, Boy.
(It was my pleasure, Mr. (Wick
.Bye
(Jonathan)
(Winston)
What are you waiting for me?
Camorra) had that contract (Santino) the key) .Will they universally
"The big table"
What about the land of Europe is?
I killed a man in the land of Europe (Oh (Jonathan
You leave me no choice but to delay the decision of complete isolation come
...The door for any service we offer
,And any attachment to land and European countries .Now closed for you
.I'm so sorry.
.Your life is over now
So why am I not dead?
.Because I didn't want to.
.Now
You have one hour, I can't delay it more than that.
.Maybe you need this
.Down the road
(Winston)
Tell them
.Tell them all
...Whoever would come
...Whoever he is
I'll kill them.
I'll kill them all
.Of course you will
(Jonathan)
(Winston)
.Payroll accounts
11,111
.During the one hour
(John Wick)
"The isolation of the final"
.Demand "11111" has been confirmed
"John Wick" "the isolation of the final" "in an hour"
""intended "with the final" kill the guy""
KhurramSultan Pakistan
subscene.com
John Wick: Chapter 3 (2019)
www.subscene.com
Visit Our Website For Free Subtitles